&gt；&gt；Steve：幸运的是有一些解决方案
&gt;&gt; Steve: Luckily there
are some solutions for
这个。&gt；&gt；steve：所以
this.
&gt;&gt; Steve: So
我使用的是ES 2015语法或ES 2015预设，
what I was using was called the ES
2015 syntax or the ES 2015 preset,
它基本上支持所有ES 2015，适用于不支持的浏览器。
which basically supports all of ES 2015,
for browsers that don't.
这意味着就像所有版本的Internet Explorermso等等，对吧。
Which means like all versions of Internet
Explorermso on and so forth, right.
所以我们要看一堆工具，所有这些都可能被使用。
And so we're gonna look a bunch of tools,
all these fall under maybe use.
但第一个可能是最有可能在所有这些情况下使用的，对吧。
But the first one is probably the most
likely to use under all of those, right.
那就是你需要看看你的用户在使用什么浏览器，
Which is you need to look at what
browsers are your users are using,
因为像Chrome、Firefox、Safari、Edge一样，它们都支持该类语法。
because like Chrome, Firefox, Safari,
Edge, they all support that class syntax.
它们都支持该语法。
They all support that syntax.
这是不是意味着你需要转移它？
Does that mean you need to transpile it?
你可能不知道。
You probably don't.
你就是不交那个税，这比交好，对吧。
You just not pay that tax,
which is better than paying it, right.
所以Babel-preset-env所做的，它有效地，
And so what babel-preset-env does,
it it effectively,
你用它而不是2015年之类的。
you use it instead of AS2015 or whatever.
基本上你可以明确你支持的是什么。
And you can basically get
specific about what you support.
这将支持每个浏览器的最后两个版本，以及它们支持的任何内容，
This will support the last two versions of
every browser, and whatever they support,
这意味着它不会转换类，最后两个浏览器。
which means it won't transpile the class,
the last two browsers.
我是说，Safari 7，
I mean, Safari 7,
你基本上是在转移一切，Safari目前是11。
you're basically transpiling everything,
Safari's currently at 11.
而且它们通常每年更新一次。
And they usually update on a yearly basis.
因此，根据我的数学计算，到2014年，也许是2013年，这取决于我们在哪里划定这条线。
So that gets you to 2014 by my math, 2013
maybe, depends on where we draw that line.
但是如果你说像，上两个版本，如果你看你的指标，
But if you said like, last two versions,
if you look at your metrics,
看看你的用户正在使用什么浏览器，你可以开始说，我不需要
figure what browser your users are using,
you can begin to say like, I don't need to
支持，我不需要转换所有客户使用的语法，
support, I don't need to transpile
syntax used by all of my customers,
对，有些就像看数据一样。
right, And
some of that is like looking at the data.
其中一部分是由产品驱动的，
Some of that is driven by product,
在LIKE产品中保留了他们支持的浏览器的列表。
at like product keeps a list
of what browsers they support.
这意味着我不需要支付喋喋不休的税
That means I don't need
to pay the babble tax for
我们并不正式支持的浏览器，对吧。
browsers that we don't officially support,
right.
所以思考这些事情是有用的。
So it's useful thinking
about those things.
很多时候我们可以用更好的工具来解决这个问题。
And a lot of times we can solve
this problem with better tooling.
很多时候，
And alot of times,
如果你的工具让你失败了，可能有一个解决方案。
if your tooling is failing you, there is
probably a solution out there for it.
你不需要接受这是命运。
You don't have to accept that as a fate.
但重要的是要考虑你愿意承担的成本
But it's important to think about what
costs you're willing to take on and
你愿意做什么取舍。
what trade offs you're willing to make.
所以让我们看看其他几个Babel插件，我认为，
So let's look at just a few other babel
plug ins that are kind of, I think,
有趣的，有用的考虑到我们今天讨论的内容。
interesting, useful considering what
we've talked about a little bit today.
这就是Babel plugin-transform-react-remove-prop-types。
So this is babel
plugin-transform-react-remove-prop-types.
REACT建议，强烈建议您使用道具类型以确保
React suggests, highly recommends that
you use prop types to make sure that
你认为他们会是什么样子？
the property is going to your component
are what you think they're gonna be?
这是一个有效的反应组件的类型系统，对吧。
It's effectively a type system for
your react components, right.
而且它只在发展中起作用。
And it only works in development.
当您进入生产模式时，REACT不会花费时间进行检查，对吧。
When you go into production mode, react is
not gonna spend the time checking, right.
只是在你发展的过程中。
It's only as you're developing.
我们不想浪费时间在你的用户电脑上检查所有的东西，
We don't wanna waste time on your users
computers to check all the stuff,
所以它完全被跳过了。
and so it just gets totally skipped.
但你还在发送代码，对吧。
But you're still sending that code, right.
你知道什么比必须解析和执行代码更快
You know what would be faster than having
to parse and execute that code and
那就永远不用了？
then never use it?
不做。
Not doing it.
[笑]对吧？
[LAUGH] Right?
所以它所做的就是基本上遍历你的代码
So what it does is it basically
goes through your code and
把它都剥了出来，对吧。
strips it all out, right.
您甚至可以说删除import语句，并且
And you can even say remove
the import statement, and
它将从属性类型中删除导入属性类型。
it will remove that import
prop types from prop-types.
有些图书馆确实需要使用它，所以你可以做其他奇怪的事情，
Some libraries do need to use it, so
you can do this other weird stuff,
这就像，嘿，如果我们不在生产中，那么做这些其他的事情。
which is like, hey, if we're not in
production than do these other things.
但我从来不需要那样的设置。
But I have never needed that setting.
老实说，这张幻灯片让我压力很大，所以
And honestly,
this slide stresses me out, so
我要搬到下一个。
I'm moving to the next one.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：babel-plugin-transform-react-purple-class-t-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2:
babel-plugin-transform-react-pure-class-t-
O-Function&gt；&gt；steve：哪个将采取反应
o-function
&gt;&gt; Steve: Which will take reaction
未保持任何状态和
components that are not
holding on to any state and
将它们转换为较小的语法。
turn them into that smaller syntax.
在反应15中并不比反应快，
Which in react 15 wasn't
any faster than react,
比类语法更好，比如类What扩展React Duct组件但是
than the class syntax, like class
whatever extends react duct component but
将来执行可能会更快，因为您不必去
may be faster in the future to execute,
because you don't have to go
通过创建类和原型链的过程。
through the process of creating
a class and a prototype chain.
上次我检查过，但这并不总是正确的。
Last I checked and
this will not always be true.
如果您使用特殊的LIKE SHORT语法
Is that if you use a special
like shorter syntax for
函数，他们只是把它变成了引擎盖下的类。
the functions, they just turned
it into classes under the hood.
但这并不是一件长期的事情。
But that is not like a long term thing.
最终他们会更快。
Eventually they will be faster.
因此，它所做的就是找到一些只有render方法的组件
And so what this does, is find some
component that only has a render method
也不会抓住任何状态。
and doesn't hold onto any state.
把它变成了一个不能前进的
And turns it into one
that does not go ahead
创建原型链的整个新类。
create a whole new class
of the prototype chain.
我们在前面的一个例子中看到，这可能是有问题的，
We saw in that one example earlier
that that can be problematic,
因为还记得我们有那个点的时候，它在一个函数内部，
because remember when we had that
point and it was inside of a function,
我们有这些原型链，但事情并不顺利？
and we had these prototype chains and
things didn't go well?
对，我们最终拍摄了800毫秒或者
Right, we ended up shooting
up to 800 milliseconds or
差不多是九个吧。
something like that compared to nine.
对，这将帮助你避免某些时候的这种情况。
Right, this will help you avoid
some of that some of the time.
现在，我不认为它会有很大的影响，但这就是为什么你要测量。
Right now,I don't think it'll have a big
effect but that's why you measure.
但反应16奠定了基础
But react 16 lays the foundation for
这实际上是为了更快，我只是不知道它是否真的已经发货了。
this actually to be faster, I just don't
know if that is actually shipped yet.
但如果你以后再看这个，这可能都是真的，我说的一切都是真的。
But if you're watching this later, this
could all be true, everything I'm saying.
如果组件具有像Babble插件那样的状态，则绝对没有任何内容。
And if a component has state like the
Babble plugin does, absolutely nothing.
因此在您现有的代码上是安全的。
So it's safe on your existing code.
我用了一个过渡。
I used one transition.
所以这很酷
So it's cool,
因为您的代码在执行时可能会变得更快，对吧。
because again your code could potentially
become faster at execution time, right.
我们总是考虑编译时间，通过线路发送的大小，但是
We always think about compile time,
the size of sending over a wire, but
此外，还必须对代码进行解析、编译和执行。
also that code has to be parsed and
compiled and executed.
如果我们能让代码更快
And if we can make that code faster,
这甚至不是JavaScript可以让它更快的东西。
that's not even a JavaScript
thing that will make it faster.
这是一个反应的东西，会让它更快。
That's a react thing
that will make it faster.
另一个，这是一种接近和亲爱的我们的心是转化或
Another one, this is kind of near and
dear to our hearts is transform or
反应内联元素。
react inline elements.
那么这是什么？为什么这么快？
So what is this and why is it fast?
它将沿着这些路线进行一些事情，这就是发生的事情。
It'll take something along those lines,
and this is what happens.
你输入这个，因为JSX不是真的，我打出来要打破它给你，它是假的。
You type this, because jsx isn't real,
I hit to break it to you, it's fake.
你通过Babble运行它，然后这个从另一端出来。
You run it through babble and
this comes out the other end.
它有一个我们调用的函数，我们在div传递它，className重要和
It has a function that we call,
we pass it at div, className important and
你好世界。
Hello World.
这些都不是动态的，对吧。
None of these are dynamic, right.
我不需要重复调用这个函数
I don't need to call this
function repeatedly and
使用相同的对象在div中传递它，并
pass it in a div with the same object and
同样的字符串，对吧，如果我们只是把它变成h1或者别的什么。
the same string in it, right,
if we're just making it h1 or whatever.
那么什么会比重复调用这个函数更快呢。
So what would be faster than
calling this function repeatedly.
现在都在一起了。
All together now.
什么比调用函数更快？
What's faster than calling a function?
不调用函数，对吧。
Not calling a function, right.
所以我实际上会把它变成这些非常有压力的物体。
So I'll actually just turn it into
these very stressful objects.
但这不是函数。
But this is not a function.
并且不调用函数更快。
And not calling a function is faster.
即使对象使您感到压力，这也是您的编译输出。
Even if the object stresses you out,
this is your complied output.
你永远不用看它，一切都会好起来的。
You never have to look at it,
it's going to be okay.
这样我们就可以避免调用一堆函数，而只需输出。
So we can avoid calling a bunch
of functions and just turn out.
无论如何，这就是函数的结果。
This is what would have come
out of the function anyway.
让我们在构建时在计算机上进行编译，
Let's do a compile time on
our computers as we build,
而不是发送功能给我们所有的用户，让他们重复这样做。
rather than sending the function to all of
our users to make them repeatedly do it.
好的，我们现在就做一次，我们会把它发给所有人，没事的，
Right, we'll just do it once now, we'll
send it off to all of them, it's fine,
大家都很开心。
everyone's happy.
我们在花哨的电脑上付款，这只是一纳秒的时间。
We pay on our fancy computers,
it's a nanosecond of time.
他们从不支付那段时间，因为它一遍又一遍地重现，对吗？
They never pay that time as it
rerenders over and over again, right?
很多时候这个构建没有考虑到
A lot of times this build
wasn't thinking about the fact
我们事先编译JavaScript，
that we compile our JavaScript beforehand,
允许我们做一些真正强大的事情，让我们的用户受益。
allows us to do some really powerful
things that benefit our users.
酷毙了。
Cool.
不做某事比做它快，如果你不得不做，
Not doing something is faster than
doing it, and if you have to do it,
您还不如在构建时在您的计算机上只做一次。
you might as well only do it once,
at build time, on your computer.
实际上，从那个插件中出来的东西实际上比那个稍微恶心一点。
What actually comes out of that plugin is
actually a little bit grosser than that.
这是真的发生的事情，但它是好的。
This is really what happens but it's fine.
就像发生过一次一样，很酷，别担心，永远不要看那张幻灯片
Like it happens once, it's cool,
don't worry, don't ever look at that slide
再说一次，我们只是想让你相信这件事没有发生。
again, we're just gonna make
you believe it didn't happen.
&gt；&gt；[笑]
&gt;&gt; [LAUGH]
&gt；&gt；steve：最后
&gt;&gt; Steve: And finally
plugin-Transform-React-Constant-Elements，类似于Reaction，
plugin-transform-react-constant -elements,
and like these exist for react,
如果你是一个棱角分明的用户，一个用户，你就会有这样的东西存在。
if you're an Angular user, an user, there
are things that exist like this for you.
我只是没有资格谈论他们，
I'm just not qualified
to speak about them,
这里有些部分是不会改变的。
which is there are parts
in here that don't change.
还记得我们看到范围实际上可以产生不同吗？
Remember how we saw scoping can
actually make a difference?
我们看到了惰性解析与急切解析。
We saw lazy parsing versus eager parsing.
我们看到了，是的，只是把东西放在错误的范围内可能会导致
We saw that, yeah, just having stuff
in the wrong scope can cause these big
问题，就像我们每次调用render一样。
problems and
like every time we call render.
再次，请记住h1并不是真正的h1，它是一个react。create元素h1，
Again, remember that h1 isn't really
an h1, it's a react.create element h1,
不管里面有什么属性，不管字符串是什么。
whatever properties are in there,
whatever the string is.
这是我们每次调用render时都会调用的一个函数。
And that's a function that we're calling
every single time we call render.
它会改变吗？
Is it ever changing?
我们为什么要这么做？
Why are we doing this?
对吧？
Right?
因为它对我们来说很容易编写，有时代码也很容易
Because it's easy for us to write,
and sometimes code that is easily
可读的你，未来的你谁是有史以来最重要的开发者。
readable by you, future you who is
the most important developer ever.
如果你受到责备，那总是六个月前的你。
If you ever get blamed something,
it's always you six months ago.
你知道现在的你和
You know about the difference
between current you and
未来的你，以及你的未来有多重要。
future you, and
how important future you is.
写可写的代码是很重要的，对吧。
It's important to write writable code,
right.
我们可以将其提取出来，并进行一系列微优化以使其更快，或者
We could extract this and do a bunch of
micro-optimizations to make it faster, or
我们可以让我们的工具基本上在构建时为我们提升那些东西。
we can have our tools just basically
hoist that stuff up for us at build time.
好的，现在我们只使用ref和ref2，即
All right so now we're just
gonna use ref and ref2, that
将运行这些函数一次，如果您想象您开始组合所有这些函数，
will run those functions once, and if you
imagine you start combining all of these,
他们开始堆积在彼此之上与他们的增量收益。
they start to pile on top of each
other with their incremental gains.
好的，现在我们有了这些函数，但是
Okay, now we have these functions, but
如果我们用另一个插件把它们变成对象，对吗？
what if we turn those into the objects
with the other plugin, right?
我们可以开始做更多的事情，实际上我们不需要做任何事情。
We could begin to do more, and
we don't actually have to do anything.
我们只是安装了一堆插件，然后让其他人的辛勤工作为我们做这件事。
We just install a bunch of plugins and
let other people's hard work do it for us.
我们受益是因为我们可以保持代码的可读性。
We benefit because we get
to keep readable code.
我们的用户受益，因为他们没有执行他们不需要的代码。
Our users benefit because they're not
executing code they don't need to.